Eddie Woods papers, circa 1957-2009 M1386
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 4: Little Magazines
  - Oculist Witnesses [Mass., Alan Davies, editor] (Includes Lewis McAdams and Gerard Malanga): No. 3, 1976 (Box 30)
  - On Foot in Surprising Amsterdam [Tom Vincent]: 1981 (Box 30)
  - On the Streets [United Kingdom]: 1978 (Box 31)
  - One World Poetry [Benn Posset]: 1979 (Box 31)
  - The Only Interruption in my Education Was When I Went to School [United Kingdom]: 1978 (Box 31)
  - Open Koffers over de Vloer [Jan van Eijk]: 1983 (Box 31)
  - Open Road [Canada]: Issue 3, 1977 (Box 31)
  - Open Road [Canada]: Issue 4, 1977 (Box 31)
  - Open Road [Canada]: Issue 5, 1977-1978 (Box 31)
  - Orange [Gérard Lalau]: 1972 (Box 31)
  - Oro Madre [Seattle, Washington]: Vol. 1, No. 3, 1982 (Box 31)
  - Oro Madre [Seattle, Washington]: Vol. 1, No. 4, 1982 (Box 31)
  - Oro Madre [Seattle, Washington]: Vol. 2, No. 3-4, 1984 (Box 31)
  - Outcrowd [United Kingdom, Rob Earl, editor]: No Date (Box 31)
  - Overthrow [New York, Dana Beals, editor] (photo of Dana Beals in EW Photos]: Vol. 4, No. 2, 1982 (Box 31)
  - Overthrow [New York, Dana Beals, editor] (photo of Dana Beals in EW Photos]: Vol. 5, No. 2, 1983 (Box 31)
  - Overthrow [New York, Dana Beals, editor] (photo of Dana Beals in EW Photos]: Vol. 6, No. 2, 1984 (Box 31)
  - Ozone Allah [Calif.]: 1978 (Box 31)
  - Paard: 1992 (Box 31)
  - Palantir [United Kingdom]: No. 15, July 1980 (Box 31)
  - P.A.N.: No. 3, 1979 (Box 31)
  - Paradiso: No. 1 (Box 31)
  - Paris Voices [K. Timmerman, editor]: No. 1, 1977-1978 (Box 31)
  - Paris Voices [K. Timmerman, editor]: No. 2, 1978 (Box 31)
  - Paris Voices [K. Timmerman, editor]: No. 3, 1978 (Box 31)
  - Paris Voices [K. Timmerman, editor]: No. 4, 1979 (Box 31)
  - Paris Voices [K. Timmerman, editor]: No. 5, 1979 (Box 31)
  - Paris Voices [K. Timmerman, editor]: No. 6, 1980 (Box 31)
  - Passion: The Magazine of Paris: No. 3, 1981 (Box 31)
  - Passion: The Magazine of Paris: No. 20, 1983 (Box 31)
  - Passion: The Magazine of Paris: No. 22, 1983 (Box 31)
  - Passion Works [Jo-Ann Zayac]: 1980 (Box 31)
  - Pax Cultura [Cape Town]: No. 5, 1983 (Box 31)
  - Peace Newsletter [New York]: March, 1983 (Box 31)
  - Il Peccato: No. 12, April 2001 (Box 31)
  - People's Yellow Pages [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 2, 1972 (Box 31)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: June, 1979 (Box 31)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: August-September 1979 (Box 31)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: No. 3, 1979 (Box 31)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: No. 4, 1980 (Box 31)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: No. 5, 1980 (Box 31)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: No. 6, 1980 (Box 31)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: No. 7, 1980 (Box 32)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: No. 8, 1980 (Box 32)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: No. 9, 1981 (Box 32)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: No. 10, 1981 (Box 32)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: No. 11, 1981 (Box 32)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: No. 12, 1981 (Box 32)
  - Performance [United Kingdom]: No. 20-21, 1983 (Box 32)
  - Performance [New Zealand]: 1979? (Box 32)
  - The Phallidomite Scandal [Yankali]: 1980 (Box 32)
  - Phantasm [Calif.]: Vo. 5, No. 3, 1981 (Box 32)
  - Pierre Reverdy [X Press]: 1978 (Box 32)
  - Planet Drum Review [Calif.]: No. 4, 1982 (Box 32)
  - Poem of a Wandering Jewess [Judith Malina]: 1982 (Box 32)
  - Poems for a Drunken Jesus [A.A. Pritchard]: 1980 (Box 32)
  - Poetry Australia: No. 52, 1974 (Box 32)
  - Poetry Flash [San Francisco, Calif., Steve Abbott, editor]: No. 141, 1984 (Box 32)
  - Poetry Flash [San Francisco, Calif., Steve Abbott, editor]: No. 148, 1985 (Box 32)
  - Poetry Flash [San Francisco, Calif., Steve Abbott, editor]: No. 155, 1986 (Box 32)
  - Poetry International: 1977 (Box 32)
  - Poetry International: 1979 (Box 32)
  - Poetry is a Place: 1978 (Box 32)
  - Poetry London / Apple Magazine: No. 2, 1982 (Box 32)
  - Poetry Review [United Kingdom]: Vol. 67, Nos. 1-2, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Poezie Explosie: 1979 (Box 32)
  - Poezie Nieuws [Benn Posset / Soyo]: No. 0, 1992 (Box 32)
  - Poezie Nieuws [Benn Posset / Soyo]: No. 1, 1992 (Box 32)
  - Poezie Nieuws [Benn Posset / Soyo]: No. 2, 1992 (Box 32)
  - Poezie Nieuws [Benn Posset / Soyo]: No. 3, 1992 (Box 32)
  - Poezie Nieuws [Benn Posset / Soyo]: No. 4, 1992 (Box 32)
  - Poezie Nieuws [Benn Posset / Soyo]: No. 5, 1992 (Box 32)
  - Poezie Nieuws [Benn Posset / Soyo]: No. 6, 1992 (Box 32)
  - Poezie Nieuws [Benn Posset / Soyo]: No. 7, 1992-1993 (Box 32)
  - Popgun Sonatas [Chicago, Lydia Tomkiw]: 1980 (Box 32)
  - Portrait of Annie/Ellen [Sprinkle]: 1982 (Box 32)
  - Poverty of Statism [Haymarket Press]: 1981 (Box 32)
  - Pressed Curtains [United Kingdom]: May, 1978 (Box 32)
  - Principia Discordia [Loompanics]: 1977? (Box 32)
  - Propaganda: No.1 (Box 32)
  - Proposta [Italy]: 1978 (Box 32)
  - Propria Cures: Nos. 16-18, 1990 (Box 32)
  - Proudhonist Materialism & Revolutionary Doctrine [Stephen Condit]: 1982 (Box 33)
  - PS Het Parool: August 2000 (Box 33)
  - Psilist: No. 1, 1984 (Box 33)
  - Puking Horse [John Bennett]: 1980 (Box 33)
  - Putting the Pages Together [Fetish Books]: 1980 (Box 33)
  - Quicksilver Messenger [United Kingdom]: No. 5 (Box 33)
  - Rage: No Date (Box 33)
  - Rags and Jewels [Paris, Sarah Bean]: 1980 (Box 33)
  - Raket: No. 2 (Box 33)
  - Raket: No. 10, 1980 (Box 33)
  - Ramp: No. 3, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Rare Tijden [Rock Against Racism]: No Date (Box 33)
  - Reagan Poems [Helen Cohen]: 1981 (Box 33)
  - Red Lettuce [K. Abbott / O. Nations]: 1974 (Box 33)
  - Red Tape [New York]: No. 4, 1984 (Box 33)
  - Rene Ricard, 1979-1980 [DIA]: 1979 (Box 33)
  - Re/Search [Calif.] (correspondence with editor Vale in Business file; associate of V. Sands): No. 3, 1981 (Box 33)
  - Re/Search [Calif.] (correspondence with editor Vale in Business file; associate of V. Sands): Nos. 4-5, 1982 (Box 33)
  - Re/Search [Calif.] (correspondence with editor Vale in Business file; associate of V. Sands): Nos. 6-7, 1983 (Box 33)
  - Re/Search [Calif.] (correspondence with editor Vale in Business file; associate of V. Sands): Nos. 8-9, 1984 (Box 33)
  - De Revolutie van 1968: 1978 (Box 33)
  - Ripped & Torn [United Kingdom, V. Sands, editor]: No. 18 (Box 33)
  - River Styx [St. Louis, Missouri]: No. 9, 1981 (Box 33)
  - River Styx [St. Louis, Missouri]: No. 10, 1982 (Box 33)
  - River Styx [St. Louis, Missouri]: No. 11, 1982 (Box 33)
  - River Styx [St. Louis, Missouri]: No. 12, 1982 (Box 33)
  - River Styx [St. Louis, Missouri]: No. 13, 1982 (Box 33)
  - Riverside Poetry Review [United Kingdom]: Vol. 1, Issue 1, 1996 (Box 33)
  - Riverside Poetry Review [United Kingdom]: Vol.1, Issue 2, 1996 (Box 33)
  - Rocking Chair: Vol. V, No. 10, 1981 (Box 33)
  - Rocking Chair: Vol. V, No. 11, 1981 (Box 33)
  - Roof [New York]: No. 10, 1979 (Box 33)
  - Roughage [Lynne Bronstein]: 1977 (Box 33)
  - Route, Route & Range [Edward Mycue]: 1977 (Box 33)
  - Sacrifice [M.G. Camarillo]: 1977 (Box 34)
  - Samisdat [Quebec]: Vol. 29, No. 4, 1981 (Box 34)
  - San Francisco’s Appeal to Reason [San Francisco, Calif.]: Vol. 1, No. 1, 1982 (Box 34)
  - San Francisco’s Appeal to Reason [San Francisco, Calif.]: Vol. 1, No. 4, 1982 (Box 34)
  - San Francisco Terror [W.Q. Foxx, editor]: September 1980 (Box 34)
  - Scar Mirror [Derek Pell]: 1978 (Box 34)
  - School of Analphabetica Bullettin [Amsterdam, Piromalli]: No. 2, 1979 (Box 34)
  - Seattle Everybody Died [Bill Butler]: 1971 (Box 34)
  - Shade [C. Bernstein]: 1978 (Box 34)
  - Shanghai Creek Fire [R.H. Miller]: 1977 (Box 34)
  - Shrew [United Kingdom]: Autumn 1976 (Box 34)
  - Simple Practice of Revolution [Phil James]: 1982 (Box 34)
  - The Singing Man [E. Mycue]: 1979 (Box 34)
  - Sipapu [Calif.]: Vol. 13, No.2, Issue 26 (Box 34)
  - Skeleton Breath, Scorpion Blush [Germany, Don van Vliet/Beefheart]: 1987 (Box 34)
  - Small Press [New York]: Vol. 1, No. 1, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Small Press [New York]: Vol. 1, No. 2, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Small Press [New York]: Vol. 1, No. 6, 1984 (Box 34)
  - Small Press [New York]: Vol. 2, No. 1, 1984 (Box 34)
  - Small Press Review [Dustbooks, Calif.]: Vol. 16, No. 10, 1984 (Box 34)
  - Small Press Review [Dustbooks, Calif.]: Vol. 17, No. 11, 1985 (Box 34)
  - Small Press Review [Dustbooks, Calif.]: Vol. 17, No. 12, 1985 (Box 34)
  - Small Press Review [Dustbooks, Calif.]: Vol. 18, No. 10, 1986 (Box 34)
  - Small Press Review [Dustbooks, Calif.]: Vol. 18, No. 12, 1986 (Box 34)
  - Small Press Review [Dustbooks, Calif.]: Vol. 19, No. 1, 1987 (Box 34)
  - Small Press Review [Dustbooks, Calif.]: Vol. 19, No. 3, 1987 (Box 34)
  - Smoking: No Date (Box 34)
  - So ‘n’ So: Visual Synt-X [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 8, 1980 (Box 34)
  - Socialism, Anarchism, and Feminism [Carol Ehrlich]: Black Bear Pamphlet 5, 1978 (Box 34)
  - The Softening of Buckingham Palace [Yankali]: 1980 (Box 34)
  - Soldier of Fortune: September 1980 (Box 34)
  - Soldier of Fortune: October, 1980 (Box 34)
  - Soldier of Fortune: July 1981 (Box 34)
  - Soldier of Fortune: August 1983 (Box 34)
  - Sombrero: No. 1, 1993 (Box 34)
  - Songs from Lily White Boys [Chris Logue]: 1960 (Box 34)
  - Sores & Roses [Fritz Hamilton]: 1978 (Box 35)
  - Sound & Vision: No. 3 (Box 35)
  - Soup [Steve Abbott]: 1980 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 9, No. 12, 1981 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 13, No. 3, 1985 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 13, No. 4, 1985 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 13, No. 7, 1985 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 13, No. 8, 1985 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 13, No. 9, 1986 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 13, No. 10, 1986 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 13, No. 11, 1986 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 13, No. 12, 1986 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 14, No. 5, 1985 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 14, No. 6, 1985 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 15, No. 1, 1986 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 15, No. 2, 1986 (Box 35)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger [South Carolina, John T. Harllee, editor]: Vol. 15, No. 3, 1986 (Box 35)
  - The Spectator [Calif.]: Vol. 1, No. 22, Issue 22, 1979 (Box 35)
  - The Spectator [Calif.]: Vol. 1, No. 23, Issue 23, 1979 (Box 35)
  - The Spectator [Calif.]: Vol. 1, No. 25, Issue 25, 1979 (Box 35)
  - The Spectator [Calif.]: Vol. 1, No. 23, Issue 23, 1979 (Box 35)
  - The Spectator [Calif.]: Vol. 2, No. 3, Issue 29, 1979 (Box 35)
  - The Spectator [Calif.]: Vol. 2, No. 3, Issue 30, 1979 (Box 35)
  - The Spectator [Calif.]: Vol. 2, No. 5, Issue 31, 1979 (Box 35)
  - The Spectator [Calif.]: Vol. 2, No. 6, Issue 32, 1979 (Box 35)
  - The Spectator [Calif.]: Vol. 4, No. 22, Issue 100, 1980 (Box 35)
  - The Spectator [Calif.]: Vol. 4, No. 23, Issue 101, 1980 (Box 35)
  - The Spectators [Andrezej Dudzinski]: 1983? (Box 35)
  - Sperlonga Manhattan Express [Italy, F. Beltrametti]: 1980 (Box 35)
  - Sphinx: Vol. 1, No. 1, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Spider Hangs Too Far From the Ground [Antonio Cisneros]: 1970 (Box 35)
  - Split Level [Canada]: Vol. 1, No. 2 (Box 35)
  - Sprinkle Report [New York]: Vol. 1, No. 4 (Box 35)
  - The Squatchberry Journal [Canada]: No. 12, 1981 (Box 35)
  - Stop [New York]: No. 3, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Straight Lines [United Kingdom] (Includes Paul Bowles): No. 7, 1983 (Box 35)
  - Strange Faeces [Opal Nations]: No. 20, 1980 (Box 35)
  - The Streets of San Miguel [Keith Wilson]: 1977 (Box 35)
  - Stroker [I. Stettner]: No. 6, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Stroker [I. Stettner]: No. 15, 1980 (Box 35)
  - Stroker [I. Stettner]: No. 16, 1980 (Box 35)
  - Stroker [I. Stettner]: No. 17, 1980 (Box 35)
  - Stroker [I. Stettner]: No. 18, 1981 (Box 35)
  - Stroker [I. Stettner]: No. 19, 1981 (Box 35)
  - Stroker [I. Stettner]: No. 21, 1981 (Box 35)
  - Stroker [I. Stettner]: No. 22, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Studio Amsterdam: No. 3, 1990 (Box 35)
  - Studio Amsterdam: No. 14, 1991 (Box 35)
  - Studio Amsterdam: No. 19, 1991-1992 (Box 35)
  - Sulphur: No. 1, 1981 (Box 35)
  - Sun & Moon (advertisement): Nos. 9-10, 1980 (Box 35)
  - Sunbury [New York]: No. 9, 1980 (Box 36)
  - Survival Manual: 1978 (Box 36)
  - Sweet Pea [Ron Padgett]: 1971 (Box 36)
  - Talking Drums Poetry Festival: 1983 (Box 36)
  - De Tand des Tijds: No. 24, 1979 (Box 36)
  - De Tand des Tijds: No. 25, 1979 (Box 36)
  - Tangerine [New York]: No. 4, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Tangerine [New York]: No. 6, 1984 (Box 36)
  - The Therapeutist [P. Aguila]: 1978 (Box 36)
  - Third Rail [Uri Hertz, editor]: No. 3, 1978 (Box 36)
  - Third Rail [Uri Hertz, editor]: No. 4, 1980 (Box 36)
  - Third Rail [Uri Hertz, editor]: No. 5, 1982 (Box 36)
  - Third Rail [Uri Hertz, editor]: No. 6, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Third Rail [Uri Hertz, editor]: No. 7, 1985-86 (Box 36)
  - Thirsty in the Ocean [Lynne Bronstein]: 1980 (Box 36)
  - Three Essays on Anarchism [Charlotte Wilson]: 1979 (Box 36)
  - To Elizabeth & Eleanor [Lita Hornick]: 1993 (Box 36)
  - Towards a Citizens' Militia [United Kingdom]: 1980 (Box 36)
  - Towards a Fresh Revolution: 1978 (Box 36)
  - Tracking [United Kingdom, T. Raworth]: 1972 (Box 36)
  - Trajectory of Passion [Melmoth]: 1979 (Box 36)
  - Transatlantic Review: Nos. 42-43, 1972 (Box 36)
  - Trash in the Streets: Vol. 1, Issue 11, 1993 (Box 36)
  - The Tree House [James Baxter]: 1974 (Box 36)
  - Tropicalism [Kenward Elmslie]: 1975 (Box 36)
  - Tumbleweed [Emanuel Ro]: 1980 (Box 36)
  - UHFO [Harrison Fisher]: 1982 (Box 36)
  - Uncramp: No Date (Box 36)
  - Unmuzzled Ox [United States, M. André, editor]: Vol. 3, No.2, 1975 (Box 37)
  - Unmuzzled Ox [United States, M. André, editor]: Vol. 4, No. 1, 1976 (Box 37)
  - Unmuzzled Ox [United States, M. André, editor]: Vol. 4, No. 2, 1976 (Box 37)
  - Unmuzzled Ox [United States, M. André, editor]: Vol. 4, No. 3 1977 (Box 37)
  - Urthkin [Calif.]: No. 1, 1978 (Box 37)
  - Urthkin [Calif.]: 1979 (Box 37)
  - Utopian Times [Calif.]: Vol. 2, Issue 3, 1976 (Box 37)
  - Vacuum Tapestries [David Gitin]: 1981 (Box 37)
  - Valium Addict [New York]: No. 3, August 1981 (Box 37)
  - Valium Addict [New York]: No. 4, 1981 (Box 37)
  - Vanishing Cab: No. 3, 1979 (Box 37)
  - ve & the Falling Iron [Ed Sanders]: 1977 (Box 37)
  - Venice Jones [Steve Richmond]: 1978 (Box 37)
  - Ving [United Kingdom]: No. 1, 1980 (Box 37)
  - Violations [United Kingdom, Paul Buck]: 1984? (Box 37)
  - A Visit to the Island of Sandy [Cienfuegos Press]: 1978 (Box 37)
  - Vlucht in de Werkelijkheid: 1983 (Box 37)
  - Voorheen de Paardekennelbode: No. 7, 1990 (Box 37)
  - Voorheen de Paardekennelbode: No. 8, 1990 (Box 37)
  - De Votre Sourire d'Enfance? [Verena Loeliger]: 1980 (Box 37)
  - The Voyeur [New York]: 1978 (Box 37)
  - Waagkrant: 1987 (Box 37)
  - Wat is er Werkelijk Loos in Nederland?: 1979 (Box 37)
  - Werktag [Germany] (mail art): Nos. 4-5 (Box 37)
  - West Coast Paria: 1975 (Box 37)
  - What Can I Say [J. Mueller]: 1981 (Box 37)
  - Whispers [North Carolina]: Vol. 3, No. 1, 1976 (Box 37)
  - Who Drank Pear Bleach [United Kingdom]: 1982 (Box 37)
  - Whos listening out there [David Anton]: 1979 (Box 37)
  - Wie Schrijft Die Blijft: 1978 (Box 37)
  - With Wine & Songs & Strange People Rushing Thru Me [Fred Pietarinen]: 1983 (Box 37)
  - A Woman Without a Country [Emma Goldman]: 1979 (Box 37)
  - The Wonderful World of Max Jacob [Fetish Books]: 1980-1982? (Box 37)
  - Woodstock Times [New York]: August 4, 1988 (Box 38)
  - Woord & Beeld: No. 4, 1980 (Box 38)
  - Work & Turn [Art Spiegelmen]: 1979 (Box 38)
  - Wrecked Hearts [San Francisco, Calif.]: March 1978 (Box 38)
  - Writ [Toronto]: 12, 1981; 13, 1982 (Box 38)
  - Writing in Holland & Flanders: No. 40, 1982 (Box 38)
  - You Should Taste What Happens To You: 1981 (Box 38)
  - ZigZag [United Kingdom]: No. 71, 1977 (Box 38)
  - ZG [United Kingdom]: No. 1, 1980 (Box 38)
  - ZG [United Kingdom]: No. 2, 1980 (Box 38)
  - ZG [United Kingdom]: No. 1, 1981 (Box 38)
- Series 5: Manuscripts by Eddie Woods
  - Eddie Woods Published Work (Primarily Published on Internet) (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Eddie Woods' Original Prose (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Eddie Woods' Original Prose (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Eddie Woods' Originals/Poems (Including Poems 1973-1977) (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Eddie Woods Prose (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Eddie Woods' Prose (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Eddie Woods' Poems (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Eddie Woods' Poems (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Eddie Woods' Miscellaneous Original Manuscripts (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Eddie Woods' Small Book of Handwritten Poems (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Eddie Woods: Poems, 1973-1977 (Original in binder) (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Bhutto and Other Love Poems 1 of 3 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Bhutto and Other Love Poems 2 of 3 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Bhutto and Other Love Poems 3 of 3 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Series 6: Ephemera, Printed Matter, Photographs, and Artwork
  This series consists of original artwork, photographs, badges, newsletters, and an extensive collection of posters. The bulk of this series is oversized.
  - Tehran Journal (2 stories edited/translated later by Eddie Woods) (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - International Times with Eddie Woods Story signed by Timothy Leary (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - The Future of Poetry and Revolutionary Bonbons (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Eddie Woods: Miscellaneous Ephemera (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Copy of Timothy Leary Playboy Interview, September 1966 (Signed by Timothy Leary) (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Reviews and Performance Announcements (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Reviews and Performance Announcements (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - International Cannabis Alliance for Reform (I.C.A.R.): Description of Audio Tapes' Contents (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Photographs by, or of, Ira Cohen (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Photographs by, or of, Ira Cohen (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Photographs by Eddie Woods (Large Format) (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Eddie Woods: Personal Photographs (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Eddie Woods: Personal Photographs Eddie Woods: Personal Photographs (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Photographs by Eddie Woods (Medium Format) (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Photographs by Eddie Woods (Medium Format) (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Photographs by Eddie Woods (Small and Medium Formats) (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Photographs by, or of, Ira Cohen (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Eddie Woods Personal Photographs (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Photographs by Peter Edel (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Photographs by Peter Edel (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Catalog of Sample Badges (Photocopy) (Box 86, Item 1)
  - Badges, Sample Book A (Box 86, Item 2)
  - Badges, Sample Book B (Box 86, Item 3)
  - Badges, Sample Book C (Box 87, Item 1)
  - Badges, Sample Book D (Box 87, Item 2)
  - Assorted Book Catalogs and Art Exhibit Announcements/Posters (Box 80)
  - Gallery Announcements (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Gallery Announcements (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Eureka! An Illustrated History of Inventions From the Wheel to the Computer [With Notes Regarding Eddie Woods' Contributions to Book] (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Gentle Ghost Newsletter No. 2 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Kirke Wilson Prints (Map-folder 1)
  - Ira Cohen Photographs (Map-folder 2)
  - Photographic Collage by Marc Morrell (Map-folder 3)
  - Honor Thy Woof, Photographic Montage (Map-folder 4)
  - Event Posters, Graphics (Map-folder 5)
  - Silkscreen Prints: Micheline, Salman Phillips, Kirke Wilson (Map-folder 6)
  - Artwork: Steve Weiss Print and Unknown Artist Print (Map-folder 7)
  - Kirke Wilson Screen Prints (Map-folder 8)
  - Drawings, Photographs, Etchings, and Other Graphics (Map-folder 9)
  - Paradiso Poster, Eddie Woods' Poem Poetry and the Punks (Map-folder 10)
  - Jack Micheline Paintings (Map-folder 11)
  - Drawings, Posters, and Announcements (Map-folder 12)
  - Event Posters (Map-folder 13)
  - Screen Prints and Photographs (Map-folder 14)
  - Painting by Jack Micheline (Map-folder 15)
  - Frank Veitmeyer (Map-folder 16)
  - Posters and Announcements (Map-folder 17)
  - The Manipulator (Journal/Magazine) (Map-folder 18)
  - Various Edith and Ernesto Levy Ephemera (Map-folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Posters (Map-folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Posters (Map-folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Posters (Map-folder 25)
  - Assorted Kathmandu Prints (Map-folder 26)
  - Melweg Posters (Map-folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Posters (Map-folder 28)
  - Jack Micheline Artwork (Map-folder 29)
  - Babette Ubink Triptych (Glass Enclosure) (Flat-box 88)
  - Posters and Announcements (Half-box 89, Folder 1)
  - Posters and Announcements (Half-box 89, Folder 2)
  - Honor Thy Woof: The Snuffie Memorial Photographic Exhibition (Description of, Photographs, and Ephemera) (Half-box 89, Folder 3)
  - Bearlock Holmes (stuffed animal), Plastic Madonna poem, Plastic Madonna and Whip, box of business cards, and volcanic ash from Jan Kerouac. (Carton 91)
  - Crippled Warlords Layout Sheets (Flat-box 92, Folder 1)
  - The Griffin 1988-1993 (The Readers' Subscription) (Box 94)
  - Honor Thy Woof: The Snuffie Memorial Exhibition Photographs (Flat-box 95)
  - Babette Ubink Letter/Poem (Flat-box 96, Folder 1)
  - Hayet Artwork (Flat-box 96, Folder 2)
  - Andrew Butcher: 40 Tearsheets, Copies of Illustrations (2 originals), and 6 Signed Original Artworks (Flat-box 96, Folder 3)
  - Artwork, Photographs, and Ephemera (Flat-box 96, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Ephemera and Photographs (Flat-box 96, Folder 5)
  - Artwork, Ira Cohen Poems, and Photographs (Flat-box 96, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Posters and Jeremiad Chants (book) (Flat-box 96, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Posters (Map-folder 39)
  - Second International Festival of the Poets (overize poster) (Map-tube 1)
- Series 7: Jenny Brookes
  This series consists of correspondence, photographs, ephemera, poems, and artwork, by, or regarding, Jenny Brookes. However, audio tapes relating to Jenny Brookes are included in Series 9. Audiovisual Materials.
  - Miscellaneous Photographs of Jenny Brookes, Her Family, and Others (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Jenny Brookes to Eddie Woods: Correspondence and Poems (1979-1987) (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Jenny Brookes to Eddie Woods: Correspondence and Poems (June 1987 - December 1997) (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Jenny Brookes to Eddie Woods: Correspondence (January 2, 1998 - March 5, 1998) (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Jenny Brookes to Eddie Woods: Correspondence (March 6, 1998 - March 31, 1998) (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Jenny Brookes to Eddie Woods: Correspondence (April 1, 1998 - April 29, 1998) (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Jenny Brookes to Eddie Woods: Correspondence (April 4, 1998 - June 30, 1998) (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Jenny Brookes to Eddie Woods: Correspondence (July 2,1998 - December 1998) (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Jenny Brookes to Eddie Woods: Correspondence (April 6, 1999 - March 14, 2005) (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Brookes, Poppy: Email Correspondence/Travel Newsletter (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Costa, Dominic: Email Correspondence/Travel Newsletter (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Jenny Brookes' Profile (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Brookes Family Tree and Brookes and Adams Brief History (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Jenny Brookes, Eddie Woods: Photographs (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Selected Poems and Drawings of Jenny Brookes (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Copies of Poems Exchanged Between Eddie Woods and Jenny Brookes (1998-2002) (Box 70, Folder 9)